localjobpositions.com 2014-07-01

# Career Opportunities In Your Area

**PRIVACY POLICY**

This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by Localjobpositions.com or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies. In addition, we may from time to time add new sites that may or may not be listed in this Privacy Policy. Please note that this policy applies only to the information collected through this website and not to websites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we link. In addition, this policy applies only to information collected by us online, not offline. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website or write to us at: 

Localjobpositions.com  
1178 South State 2nd Floor  
Orem Utah 84097 

To opt-out of future marketing communications please click Unsubscribe

**About Information We Collect and How We Use It.**

We may collect some or all of the following types of information (collectively, "Information"): 

(1) Personal Information. When you visit our site, we will ask you to provide some personal information about yourself, including your name, address, telephone number(s), e-mail address(es) and other information specific to your personal circumstances. 

(2) Cookies and Tracking Information. When you visit our site, we send one or more cookies to your computer or other device. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including for storing user preferences, improving search results and ad selection, and tracking user trends, such as how people search. To improve our services, we also track information about what web-site you were on before coming to our site, what web-site you visited when you left our site, and whether you return to our site. 

(3) Log Files. We also collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), the browser you used to visit our site, the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

(4) Third Party Tracking. We also sometimes use third party advertisements to support our site. Some of those advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send those advertisers information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geo targeting purposes (showing information or advertisements specific to the area where you live) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited. 

(5) User communications. When you send email or other communications to us, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. When you send and receive SMS messages to or from one of our services that provides SMS functionality, we may collect and maintain information associated with those messages, such as the phone number, the wireless carrier associated with the phone number, the content of the message, and the date and time of the transaction. We may use your email address to communicate with you about our services. 

(6) Affiliated Services on Other Sites. We offer some of our services on or through other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to us in order to deliver the service. We process such information under this Privacy Policy. 

(7) Third Party Applications. We may make available third party applications, such as gadgets or extensions, through its services. The information collected by us when you enable a third party application is processed under this Privacy Policy. Information collected by the third party application provider is governed by their privacy policies. 

(8) Unique application number. Certain services we may offer can include a unique application number that is not associated with your account or you. This number and information about your installation (e.g., operating system type, version number) may be sent to us when you install or uninstall that service or when that service periodically contacts our servers (for example, to request automatic updates to the software). 

(9) Other sites. This Privacy Policy applies to our services only. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results, sites that include our applications, products or services, or links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. 

(10) Other Uses of Information. We may also use the information we collect to provide, maintain, protect, and improve our services (including advertising services) and develop new services, and to protect our rights or property and that of our users. 

**Cookies**

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some site features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. 

We may use the DoubleClick advertising cookie on AdSense partner sites and certain of our own services to help advertisers and publishers serve and manage ads across the web. You can view and manage your ads preferences associated with this cookie by accessing the Ads Preferences Manager. In addition, you may choose to opt out of the DoubleClick cookie at any time by using DoubleClick's opt-out cookie, located at http://www.google.com/ads/ preferences/plugin/. 

**Information sharing**

We are in the business of identifying the needs of prospective clients for other third parties, and providing information to those third parties, including your email address, so that they may offer goods or services to the prospective clients. By entering our web-site, you are consenting to our sharing of the above-described information to third parties who will use that information to offer you goods or services. These services include, but are not limited to, information and opportunities regarding higher education. 

Localjobpositions.com may disclose the information we collect from and about you as follows: (1) to the employment or educational organizations from whom you have requested information or the employment or educational organization we have matched based on your interests; (2) to our email and data hosting service providers, if the disclosure will enable them to perform a business, professional or technical support function for us; (3) as necessary if we believe that there has been a violation of the Localjobpositions.com Site Terms of Use or of our rights or the rights of any third party; (4) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law; (5) to our select partners and affiliates that we believe may have offers of interest to you; and (6) as described to you at the point of collection. 

You also agree to receive email marketing from Localjobpositions. Any email you receive will be from Localjobpositions and may be sent by our mailing partner. At times, you may request that your information be submitted to another site. It is possible that the selected site will not accept your information for various reasons, including that you are out of the area which the site serves, or your request duplicates another you already made. Localjobpositions has no control over this occurring. In addition, even though a site does not accept your information, both we and that site may store your information and your information may subsequently be utilized to send to you offers or follow-up e-mails from Localjobpositions, one of our partners or affiliates, or by the site which did not originally accept your information. By entering and using our site, you are consenting to such offers or follow-up e-mails being sent to you. In addition, we will share your Information with others when we have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Localjobpositions, its users or the public as required or permitted by law. 

By registering on this Site, you agree that this act constitutes an inquiry and/or application for purposes of telemarketing laws, and notwithstanding that your telephone and/or cell number may be listed with the federal Do-Not-Call Registry you expressly opt-in to: (a) receive an offer or service from one or more of our partners or affiliates; (b) receive future information about products and services from us, our partners, affiliates and other third parties to whom we may provide your information; (c) permit us, our partners, affiliates and other third parties to contact you pursuant to the business relationship we have established using the information you provided to us for any purpose such as contacting you by e-mail address, phone and/or mobile phone number (including use of automated dialing equipment), text (SMS) message or any means of communication for any purpose that, among other things, your wireless device may be capable of receiving (e.g. mms, video etc. ). 

We also sometimes disclose the Personal Information we collect to companies that operate various services for us such as marketing distribution, advertising, or certain product functionalities. These vendors only have access to Personal Information needed to perform their functions, and may not share it with others or use it for any other purpose. We only share your email address with our mailing partner, All Inbox, LLC, for the purpose of sending you relevant third-party emails. 

We may share aggregated information (i.e., information about you and other customers collectively, but not specifically identifiable to you) and other non-personal, de-identified, or anonymous information we collect with third parties, including affiliates to develop and deliver targeted advertising on our Site and on the websites of third parties. If you would prefer that we do not utilize cookies with your website experience, or would prefer to restrict the use of cookies with network advertising associates, please see the "Choices" section above. 

We may be required to share your Personal Information with law enforcement or government agencies in response to subpoenas, court orders, federal/state audits or similar circumstances. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law. 

As with any other business, it is possible that in the future, our company could merge with or be acquired by another company. If such an acquisition occurs, the successor company would have access to the information maintained by us, including your Personal Information, customer and business account information, but would continue to be bound by this policy unless you consent otherwise. 

**Accessing and updating personal information**

When you use our services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your Personal Information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), 

or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Because of the way we maintain certain services, after you delete your information, residual copies may take a period of time before they are deleted from our active servers and may remain in our backup systems. 

Federal and state regulations may require that we maintain certain information (including your personal information) submitted through our website for various time periods. In order to comply with these regulations, we cannot delete your information from our database if to do so is not permitted by an applicable law or regulation. 

**Children**

This website is not intended for persons under 18 years of age. These products and services are not developed or directed at children. We do not knowingly collect or retain information in connection with this site from children under the age of 18. We do not ask a child under age 18 for personal information. If you are under the age of 18, please leave this site immediately. 

**California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits users of this site who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for such third parties' direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to us at 297 Kingsbury Grade STE 100 , Stateline NV 89449- 4470\. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page. We will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review. 

By using this site, you signify your assent to our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. When you request information through us, you are authorizing us to share information with third party marketing advertisers or companies, who may contact you by any of the user communications described above. If you do not want further communication from them, please notify the third party marketing advertisers or companies directly. Also you may unsubscribe to us at unsubscribe We reserve the right to make changes in this policy at any time. Please check the policy each time you use our website to ensure you are aware of any changes in our privacy practices. Our Privacy Policy will indicate the date it was last updated. Your continued use of our site will signify your acceptance of the changes to our Privacy Policy. 

_Last modified: June 27, 2013_
